everything elicits so many responses and
you gotta like
you have to you have to battle with
yourself and you're like no
that thing right there is a different
color than everything else
and i just something tells me just keep
keep at that
that that that's actually our self
is developed through that time and
there's something about the way that
you're talking about it and how
literal it's been for you that's really
having me see
more of the structures of the things
that
i'm looking at and working with it's
really great
[Music]
hi everyone i'm mercury black and i'm
here today with guy senstalk
and we're just gonna jump right into
this so um
as we were saying before we started
recording guy there's
something going on at the moment like
both the intellectual dark web the
intellectual deep web the intellectual
light web there seems to be a larger
thing operating
that jordan peterson which the channel
started around his work
um through john verveigh yourself um
jonathan pagio paul vander clay there's
something going on at the moment what do
you think it is
because you're clearly participating
yeah totally
and i think i'm i'm i'm i'm along with
everybody that at least i know who i've
talked to
i think would probably say something
very similar which is
we're all really excited about what
we're doing together
and if you ask us what we're doing we'll
be like i don't
know exactly he asked us
who we doing it for we're finding out
as we're doing it right there's this
there's this um
there's there's something about i don't
know exactly what it is but i know
i know that it it is um it has a feeling
as a feeling of the feeling
i get about everything that's felt like
this
has been good right for me um
there's kind of a quality of emergence
like
like a sense of like i'm i'm listed i'm
listening to some whisper
right that i don't i start to realize
i've been following
a lot longer than i thought as it
reveals itself
right um and
i think along the way i've got little
hits of
of what we're doing right because for me
i just started this
i i really actually didn't have any
intention other than
[Music]
having a sense of listening to podcasts
and thinking
there's so much more you could do with
these things like i ah
you know and being a circler um and
doing circling which
we'll talk about a little bit too but i
i was sensing like there's so much more
available
in a conversation so i was like okay so
i'll stop complaining about it and i'll
just start doing a podcast
and i'll just start inviting interesting
people on and try to hit a sweet spot
my this is my only intention try to hit
a sweet spot between like a normal
conversation
and something like circling and see if i
can just
feel into that place and it so happens
that the first person i
i officially
had on my channel was um
was john vervicky and
i totally by the time i started talking
with him within seconds i
i like totally forgot that i was
videoing
i forgot any of my intentions and at the
end of it he was kind of like
whoa this was really different and i was
like oh yeah there's a this we're doing
and it that started a friendship with
him and i
and and then just through that
and other people um apparently
you know that came rebel wisdom
right a lot of these threads that i'm
sure a lot of people listening are
familiar with
um on some
some of that stuff i already knew about
but it wasn't a cohesive thing for me
um and now i'm finding myself after the
fact being part of some kind of
conversation or some kind of dialogue
that a lot of what the dialogue has
become about
is understanding the thing that we're
experiencing together
um and it's
it's fascinating that way i was just
thinking about as i have a
uh a new client of mine who's
turns out he was a he was like a math
major he was really into bath
and we started to talk about like well
what is it that glows for you about math
and he started to say yeah you know what
it is
he's he's like when you do the formula
like you know what the next step is but
you don't know where that's going to
lead you and it's that sense of
a sense that you're heading in the right
direction
but it's not really clear but then when
you get there
and he says like i got the sense of like
the language trail that you
leave that you lead through all of that
is like when you look back it's called
the formula
it's the mathematical formula but while
you're in it
right it's just this process of like the
sense of concealment
or withdrawal that's like that you
that that's that's concealed but it's
drawing you
and then it's revealed right and then
you start to understand what you were
that whatever that sense is that weaving
together
that process i'm familiar with and it
just feels like it's happening on a much
bigger more public
way than i've ever experienced it that
reminds me of like when i've heard
jordan peterson talk about i think
piaget's
um childhood development models where
there's a level of childhood where the
children can play a game together
none of them can describe what the game
is they're capable of playing it but
remove it
and they can't describe what they're
doing perhaps this group
is the toddler form of the
like ken wilbur's integral stage and
then this group is beginning to do
something new that's emerging
but is it the toddler form where we're
going to have to play the game for a
while
before we'll be able to verbalize or
even really understand what it is
and so where do you get the faith to
dive
into that because it sounds to me like
and for me it's
i long ago just i turned over my will to
god and said look you just tell me what
i'm supposed to do and i'll follow right
so when you talked about
feeling out the good and following that
that's what led me to doing all of this
but i've done it in such a crazy
mystical way
right i know how much faith it takes
to act that way what's what's giving you
the faith to follow this right feeling
and especially in such a public way yeah
when you don't even know exactly what it
is you're doing totally
the thing for you i really heard i
really got it i felt i felt like i saw a
glimmer of it when you're talking about
it
a very int like the faith it takes i
think you said to
go that way or to be that way
what what is it like what how did you
what's your experience of that
well mine is when i became bipolar like
full-on i got hit by a bus
and that triggered my first mania when i
was 26 i was crossing the street
and so the psychiatrists say i had the
genetic predisposition
and it was the traumatic event but it
was full-blown mania and
complete psychosis where and not
not the mystical powers i have now it
takes time to refine that this is an out
of control
psychosis right and for the first
five years it was just a horrible cycle
for me in and out of mental institutions
against my will
my original cycles were three years long
with two years of depression
and it was because god just
hammered me out of my old life like nope
can't live like that like hammer
hammer hammer until i had to realize
okay
i meant to walk some different path and
then i went into isolation
so after my second major breakdown um
the government was like look we don't
need to be replacing cop car windows or
burdening the hospital with you when
you're in a delusion that the world's
already
ended just go on permanent disability
see if you can get yourself under
control
and my first two years i didn't tell my
friends where i'd moved
i didn't have a phone internet or car um
my siblings i didn't have them visit i
only saw my parents and mostly just to
drop supplies
and for me it was i wasn't gonna survive
life
unless i turned over to god i was one of
those ones where he put me right in the
edge where
i couldn't turn away from him and
survive
it was i was hammered with
just things beyond my control so that i
had to turn
weeping to god and eventually learn to
say
okay thank you for these hardships show
me where this goes and what this is
meant to teach me and make
and it's taken over a decade of living
that way to lead me to where i am now
and
it led to like andrew joachim is the one
who started sorting myself
out based on peterson's self-offer right
at one point my angel told me to message
him i came across his video
with peterson and um my angel told me to
subscribe i'd help him later
eventually i messaged andrew and we
ended up becoming friends and he used me
somewhat like a mentor for a while
eventually when he wanted to quit doing
the channel he asked me to take it over
and my angel confirmed it was something
i had to do
um and i couldn't do it on my own so i'm
lucky he asked like me and ryan together
to team up um
so yeah for me it's that crazy and the
experience
like i'm not claiming what objective
reality is i'm just saying phenomenal
logically
it's as though when i got hit by the
boss i moved into a fantasy
right where the metaphysical is all real
and i don't know if my own
illusion or a real angel objective yeah
whatever it is it's good it's a delusion
it's a good delusion
yeah just be better behaved keeps
and if it's real then it appears to be a
good angel because listen right
has done good things yeah yeah
i uh it's interesting when you
when you when you talked about like the
the the place where you got
it brought you all the way to the edge
right
one there's something that sounds very
familiar about
that like it's something's really
familiar about it but i just it struck
me
it's like oh yeah like i think what i
heard you say is like it's when
is when like what was possible became
what was necessary
like what was necessary
and what was possible were the same
thing at one point
and what happened when you went into the
when you went into isolation
was it was it were you it was a i got
this picture of you kind of like
bat like going at it with the demons in
your head and like
working that out is that what it was
yeah yeah like working on my internal
environment the self-worth the shadow
work the self-understanding meditation
teaching myself to meditate also that
was a full-time
job for about four years right two years
of total isolation then
i got a phone and internet i started
allowing the occasional person to visit
and i've opened up to the world but
i still don't interact with the world
outside of the youtube
yeah it's yeah like i'm on a farm um
i leave my houses and i go out into
nature but i don't go into society i
still get all my supplies dropped off
i live in my own magical world with all
my protection
spells and shields um yeah so i live in
my own mystical world
right and i told god like i'm just gonna
worry about my own self
if the world needs the universe wants
anything from me it will come and ask
yeah and that grew over the years where
first it was an individual would come
into my life for something
i'd help them and it's as it went it was
a part of my training as well
and then just eventually it naturally
led without me choosing to
because i let go completely of outcome
um whatever i just want whatever's good
to happen but by god's definition of
good
and at one point what's good for
everyone is that i crash this channel
and stop doing it because that's what
serves everyone best
but hey i'm fine with that i just want
to play my part in the game
whatever wow there's a way yeah it's
funny it's like as you're talking about
this i'm kind of feeling into like well
what is it that you have
faith in right and
when i get i what's i can fee i can see
it in your
in the the way that your mannerisms are
kind of gathering
right in in your speech almost like this
this kind of sense of like yeah i'm just
gonna do what it says
and i'm gonna let go of the results and
pay attention
because this quality of just like the
sense of where
yeah what is like what the the horizon
of possibility
and the necessity that that possibility
creates are
very taut in
in this world i appreciated what you
said it's like i don't know if this is
objective reality or not it doesn't even
matter phenomenologically
this is the way the world worlds itself
around me and through me and then
this quality that that's how we all live
like i was that way even before just it
was so stable i could imagine it was
objective reality but donald hoffman's
work shows
none of us are in objective reality this
is a user interface that consciousness
creates
that obviously would evolve to show us
fitness payoffs
not objective reality so it made me
realize i was
always living in a world i was
hallucinating just it used to be more
stable
and so now i know that you don't live in
the same universe i live in
right there's something underneath this
song but you're
a generator of an entire universe that
you're the center
right that you manifest out of this
reality yeah i'm the same thing
shining down in a different location
manifesting another universe
yeah briz is a very quiet universe right
now
also experiencing this conversation and
we together
almost like indra's net like we together
co-create the greater reality
by each inhabiting our own right
so there's a way in which because i've
always thought this about i
i've had a bunch of friends who are who
are bipolar
and all of them are brilliant and i
always have the sense of like
first of all i always i was always like
man if if i was
bipolar i would i would have so much
trouble not getting like wanting the
highs
because the highs look so amazing
right they look so amazing um i mean the
lows are
are crazy but the
there's a gene there's a genius in
that that's something about like the
sense of the middle
of like staying tethered to whatever it
is that
one tethers to and that is the sweet
spot and it seems treacherous it always
with all of it it just looks really
treacherous to me
my advantage was like the poor part the
time period where i really started
sorting myself out
it was after spending two years in
isolation already doing the work
kind of on my own and then my archangel
stepped into me and the other reason
like my faith is so easy for me
and i wondered about you is it's not
like i read about an archangel
and tried to contact it and it's like
it's something i only understand in
theory
phenomenologically to me my archangel is
real yeah it interacts with me it's
undeniable
yes and as i interact with it and when
it predicts something it happens
right when it tells me to do something
yeah
it ends up being good even if it takes
time
and i don't see how at first so like to
me
it's i'm kind of cheating it's a
shortcut it's not fair to compare my
faith
to grizzes he hasn't [ __ ] met an
angel i was lucky one just
marched right into my world and shook my
reality and
didn't go away like as i say that i can
feel his hand on my shoulder
and just was never not there for me
except sometimes when i'm really
struggling and i ask for help
he just goes i'm here and i'm like okay
i need help and he goes no
and just send me someone no why you can
do this
just know i'm right here yes i know he's
going to help yes i know you're in
hell okay you can do this climb out on
your own
right but he's never not there right
it sounds like in those incidents is it
fair to say like he's the
he's the voice letting you know that
faith
yes yes
and also like he's him combined with
simple meditation and self-discovery
is how i've learned everything so later
i became very interested in peterson and
sam harris and
you know tons of alan watts terence
mckenna island more
but those aren't where i learned this
stuff it's
i got drawn to that for the enjoyable
confirmation bias of
here's peterson explaining something i
discovered here's sam harris explaining
something else
i was really taught in that ancient way
of that god will just drive you [ __ ]
bonkers
all the cavemen push you off into a cave
and
something divine that only you see shows
up to do your training
yes i've played that ridiculous role
right right at the moment
right and the set this sense the sense
of
um so on another level i think what i'm
kind of getting is on
one level the thing about like that you
could say that i think you said like
i don't think you said this but you said
like the cheat you got the cheat sheet
because everything's just so personified
and articulated and speaks directly to
you that
it's almost like you get oh it's like
where
someone else may have to see through
many layers of reality
to hear the echo of that voice over time
you're just like
there it is he's like nope i'm not
coming you can do it yourself
or other times yeah comes right in and
guys
don't worry here's what you need to know
here's what you need to do
so it's not always [ __ ] it you're on
your own but occasionally it's no no
we did this to you on purpose and you
can get out so it's
not it's a it's a dialogue
oh yeah yeah living you're living in a
conversation
your reality speaks with you
and it's not even just that archangel i
connect to other things i also
i've experienced miracles or magic or
prayers working
i experience either either i'm psychic
and an empath or i experience delusions
of being
psychic and an empath yeah i've had
dreams that come
true and where i've told someone else
the details before
it came true so yeah i know i'm not
editing my own memory of the dream
the way a skeptic might say what you're
doing um i
put [ __ ] to the test and it's always
come up like ding ding ding
metaphysicals real take it seriously huh
yeah i can feel i it's funny it's really
interesting because
at least my experience of talking to you
i'm noticing as you're speaking the the
one
the the one who is the one understanding
what you're saying
it's like the world kind of looks a lot
more concrete
it's really what do you mean expand on
that yeah just like a sense of
just that sense of like no it's not some
subtle
kind of thing third echo of something
like that and it goes
no you are going to do that or you will
do that like
there's this quality of of um
clarity of articulation
that seems very very direct and i
am finding myself in wonder of it
and a bit jealous of it honestly
i think that's the feeling of like kind
of just actually just appreciating
appreciating the actually if we say
we look at rationality in terms of ratio
like or ration it's very
rational right it's like you when you
went into isolation you got really clear
and you rationed
right you rationed your social
connections you rationed everything
so you could listen to the one voice or
the multiple voices that were
speaking to you it's it it doesn't sound
crazy to me it sounds actually
less crazy to me and it's in an
interesting way i'm just a free i'm
appreciating walking in your world a
little bit
and that's that's the joke that's why
god picked knees it's intentionally a
joke to take an old punk who chained
smokes and gets high
while he's talking to doctors and
priests rambling about psychotic
delusions it's to show that god has a
sense of humor
and i don't mind that i'm a punchline
it's fun like i get that god's not
laughing at me it's with me
um and to me it's a bit of freedom as
well because i've realized
there is something to deep teachings
needing to be preserved from the masses
that you know like the way certain
orders you know hermetic orders preserve
deep teachings i feel the fact that i'm
the lunatic magician
gives me more freedom to voice deep
truths because there's a very plausible
deniability
for a person who's at that materialist
level or is a fundamental christian who
would find
my deep truths damaging for them it's
very easy i've got like to just
disregard me
it's he's crazy he's got no authority
there's
no reason i shouldn't have to i can
dismiss that if i wish
so i feel it's safer for me to say
certain things whereas
if someone like jordan peterson or sam
harris said it they've got so much
authority
that it's gonna not give as many people
the free will
option to remain in denial of the divine
or to remain
at a lower level of enlightenment yeah
you know it's interesting as you're
saying that it's reminding me of
something i've been
you know trying to like it's a little
bit of what we were talking about before
but this sense this sense of
what i what i love about poetry right
and is that it can is it can presence
the unknown
without kind of raping it of its
own right it's like it can presence up
the unknown without making it known
there's a certain because if you make
there's certain things that are
are they they need to be
they are in that they're concealed and
their concealedness
can be revealed and i think our sense of
that
in my experience and i think our
like quickening age of technology is can
our ability to perceive that is so
less and less and less and less and less
we only see things that we can
extract stuff out of and get really
clear on and have a position
but the sense of like at the edges the
the um
the angelic if you will the the the
numinous the
the things that the mythical like the
the mystic those things that can only be
preserved right
presence in presence in their
in their in their withdrawal in some
sense so it's like the right
relationship and i just got that sense
of like yeah
oh yeah i because i'm crazy like i can
say this [ __ ] right
and they can it still preserves
something right
also it's like i'm not claiming to have
a proper truth
i'm just claiming i've touched something
beyond me yeah and that this is
faulty this isn't the final word it's
like we're all
the blind men touching an elephant yeah
i've just grabbed a different part than
you have
yeah but what you know you know things
about the elephant either
briz knows things neither of us do and
i'm not claiming to be correct
i'm aware that i'm more correct than i
used to be and i hope to be more correct
in the future
but it's scale it's not right or wrong
and i'm definitely not right
right i'm just trying to do my best this
that which just knows that
that which that knows what is that can i
ask you
so that that kind of goes like look i
may i maybe
i may be right and maybe not look i'm
just continually
i don't know right there's a there's a
sense of like
you know there's something that you know
there
or that's guiding you there how do you
know that well there's two places one is
there's that place sam harris talks
about of naked awareness
where beneath all your egos sub
personalities and everything
there is something that's just a pure
awareness
that is one with all right and the other
is the like in the high magical
traditions the higher
self the part of you that can in fact
my holy guardian angel and my higher
self
sometimes are indistinguishable
sometimes i'm not sure
sometimes they merge sometimes they
separate
and sometimes i'm not sure if that's
coming from my higher self
or my holy guardian angel yet i'm also
aware that's because both of those
beings
are so high that they're really the same
thing and that's also christ
and it's also your higher self yeah it's
also grizzes
and it's everyone watching and that when
you get up to that point we're all one
thing
anyway yeah totally yeah totally
but we're diving too much into mean we
promise
but also just know i see the light in
you as well
like you work with the same parent
corporation i do i see that
right so if there's anything i can do
for you you want to work on getting in
touch with anything i'm in touch with
we can do private sessions or um but
just yeah i'm up
yeah i'm a fan of the whole project you
and all your friends
so whatever we can do here at sorting
myself out
but also on a one-to-one level um you
and i can work on things so
i'm not cutting you off at digging into
my lunacy
totally i'd love for the audience to get
a little bit about circling and you
um before we go on about me too much
totally well it's interesting circling
things
it's funny it's funny the thing that
just happened
like in a certain way of just like who
are you like what's and then
noticing what it's like being you i
wasn't even thinking about circling i
was just but that's
essentially it's that that basic i thou
connection to be able to kind of see to
be able to
i was actually made a little video today
today i've been doing these little
videos lately i don't know exactly
why something something about
because i've just been doing you know
these i've only been posting these
these dialogues that i've been having
but i haven't really just posted just
things but i've been just doing these
little things where i'm like
taking a walk and i and just start
talking about something
and they're taking on a little life of
their own i'm noticing
and and i was just talking about today
this sense of what bluebird calls the i
vow
right like martin buber the the the
you could say he's he's kind of you
could say he's kind of an existentialist
theologian jewish i'm not familiar with
him
yeah so so he he basically says
the way he puts it is like so human
beings
right are a relationship
and you in the way he kind of he kind of
poetically puts it is that
that we are either in an uh an eye thou
relationship
or an it relationship and
what he says is um there's a way in
which
when you're an i it relationship the it
is an it by virtue as whatever it is
that you're relating to as a means
to an end right and he says the ayat
relationship
right is the world of time and space
right and he says
the i vow relationship is harder to
describe
but when when when you become thou
right um you are not a means to an end
you're an end in itself right
so there's that quality of like you kind
of what what uh
i think kilik would say
you know of dwelling on what is of
ultimate concern
it's almost like if you took the concern
and you saw it
and faced it it's like like kind of like
the place wherever the whole world
gathers in that moment and time
disappears
and i becomes through thou and thou
becomes through i
right and
there's i would say that like you could
look at it like this
that did the our ability
we kind of look at yeah if we look at it
in kind of booberology if you will
which i i really like um starts to
architect like it starts to
you could start to see how it it reveals
the you could say the
the structure of the intimate integrity
integrity of relations that
have human beings be the way that we are
right
and that that relation i it
is one that that that you can
you can make people in it
right in ways that are really obvious
but there's also ways in which you can
make people in it
in a very subtle way right so it's like
and here's and here's the thing about it
is that as burberry would say
i yet and i thou is always spoken as one
word
right so it's not to get the like that
like the ontological depth of this or
the existential
nature of this it's not like i'm a i
that then relates to an it or an
i that relates to a vowel no it's
they happen as one right they're like
spoken as one word so it's
the different eye that arises when you
become thou
right then an eye that arises when you
become it
so i would say in that moment right as i
was like
kind of getting your world and kind of
speaking and just following my interest
and you were kind of
disclosing yourself to me i disappeared
for a little bit you're like hey
like let's let's stop thinking let's
talk about circling i was like
oh [ __ ] time and space kind of came back
together
circling i would say is
is really it's a practice of it's
you could say it's kind of like a a yoga
of a by that
it's a it's a
i like to use the analogy of circling as
a
practice which is really what it's
become
it's gotten known to be it's a
relational practice a relational yoga
whereas just like a yoga class right you
really a yoga class here you're doing
these postures you're going you're
basically taking basic body
spotty mindsets right and you're
breaking them
archetypes the acetas and you just go
into a class and you go
deep in these asanas right such that
when you walk out
when you're walking down the street or
the next day and you're not even
thinking about the yoga class you took
your baseline in all your relations with
your body and mind and degravity is just
a lot more open right if we said that
like
i though or relationships if we like
imagined we made them like asanas and we
got together and we did a yoga class or
a
relational yoga classes we just go in
these deep
deep dives into these asadas and
exercise the machinery if you will to
use
for veggies language that that
lie under deep deep connections
um such that when you walk away and
then you're talking to your wife or your
husband you're just a little bit more
open
in your response right you can see them
more you can like share yourself more
you can be
a lot more uh
relationally available to your world
right
and the nourishment that comes with that
and from everything because you know
i've heard you speak before
um from everything i've put together
about the way you view
circling it seems to me that what you do
with
another person to create the i vow
for me magic is that you can also do
that with every other aspect of reality
yes you can do that with a rock with a
tree and you can do it with the virgin
mary
or krishna um and that you can do it
with your own sub personalities you can
do it with
the very nature of reality you can learn
to have that
with anything that there's some sort of
hand psychism i
suppose or that to me it's it seems that
the like from the cavalier the hermetic
principle that
all is mine um right that seems to me
accurate
um from my interaction with the world so
it
seems that like just what i'm doing with
my angel is very similar to what you're
doing with another human being
yeah um yeah
anyway how how did you get how did you
discover it for yourself
for yourself
like a really [ __ ] up childhood
okay it's funny i was like one time
uh jerry and i who were we were the two
that basically
had the experience with the group of
group of people
um at burning man in the middle of the
night
spontaneously it just circling happened
and and we basically jerry and i walked
away
and it was him and i that looked at each
other and we were like
that thing that just happened like we
didn't have a word for it but we both
pointed to it and we knew exactly
what we that there was something there
that we didn't have a word for
that was distinct from all the other
things that we were doing that were kind
of like that
something spoke and we just both
spontaneously
brought our hands out and shook shook on
it and we had no idea exactly what
that meant 20
to 23 years later right with the help of
a lot of different people
right um and a lot of
like a lot of fumble [ __ ] you're like
your way through like beating our head
against the wall
realizing things but still listening to
that same thing that we're pointing to
like whatever that is um
i feel like i'm still listening to it
and and just like the mathematician i
was talking about before
right occasionally
i can i like i look up and i look at
the length of time right
and the trail that that like listening
to it made
right and you have this practice called
circling in
in all over the world and people
participating in it but my experience
has really been and i think this has
been my role
in circling is kind of feel
in a sense that it's more like i've been
responding to something
that's been illuminating to me and
and in some in so many ways if you look
at on paper if you look at some
other people would say like to the just
watch me on camera you go like ah you
really created something
you built something and from a certain
age like that is true
but from from the outside i think that
is true and it's fair to talk about it
like that
but from the inside what was driving all
that building it was actually
really paying attention to something
that was emerging and is still emerging
and that's the sense i get from
that i picked up from you and it's like
with me often in these conversations
whether it's private sessions or a
podcast
as i'm speaking i enter this flow state
and
i have to sort of just to maintain all
the nonsense inside myself i've had to
learn pretty much
constant mindfulness but i'm always
aware of what's arising
but sometimes during these podcasts and
i can feel it happening now
i start to step back into my awareness
and
i begin to experience myself the same
way i experience
you that i don't know what you're gonna
say next i just see you happening
and i begin to experience myself just
happening where
i don't know the end of the sentence i
really don't know where i was going with
this
other than i wanted to express this
certain feeling
and it's almost like there's a waterfall
coming down
of juggling balls and i'm just grabbing
them the ones that drop
and like passing them on teeth and it
seems to just be this weird
thing that i do naturally the same way
birds thing
and that i realized i don't even have to
put the effort into this
as i described it i've fallen right back
into
right now i feel this deep part of me is
kicking back
like with its feet up and it's arms
behind its head going like watch
this just talks on its own it will just
keep going
and right yeah right now i'm
experiencing you and me the same way
yeah it's both just happen yes
but i've learned the difference between
you learn to feel the energies of what's
coming and you know what to allow
so i'm not claiming i only channel good
[ __ ] i've got all these inner demons
it's i know the smell of them i know the
flavor of them i know like
i know what i'm connecting to now and
when it's
good i can just let it go and when it's
dark
that's when okay i've got to step in and
manage this yes like you're not taking
the seat
you're not free to talk on youtube yeah
we're gonna do some work and discuss
why you're saying that right now this is
okay for
ego to step in and take control yeah but
when it's
all angels and light then i can step
back and just let it all happen
totally in that i get that sense of that
that which can start to tell with
greater and greater acuity i imagine
the difference between the two like you
can't you don't
even what i'm hearing you say is i can't
really even articulate how i know
but there's something that's tracking
something that just
knows and the more that it tracks its
ability to
to track and hit the sweet spot
right so there's something there's
something about these
it's also about following the moral code
so that your conscience is clean
that you're one to me it's the seven
natural laws don't lie
don't steal don't kill don't rape don't
assault
don't coerce don't trespass yeah and
then
you follow that hard and you do your
shadow work you learn mindfulness
you take full responsibility for
yourself
you stop blaming anything else it's i
can't control the outer world i just
control me
yeah and you line up it's like peterson
says tell the truth and you feel [ __ ]
line up and stuff
and it's we've got all these natural
psychic abilities internal
guidance systems and we've got a variety
of desires
uh drives impulses inspirations
yeah and it's about when you follow
honesty
like really take a vow of honesty and
aim at the good
where you have to be honest with the
world and yourself and the universe will
correct the rest for you
you can learn every other deep wisdom
just by taking a vow of honesty
and aiming is the good then you need to
you need to learn mindfulness of course
you can't
work on the self when you don't know
what the self is
and you have to know the lower case self
from the highest
right it's all energies and experiences
but then [ __ ] lines up
and your internal meters start working
better and your delusions start making
sense
before you've done all this when you get
tap into the mystic realms
you project all your shadows and
nonsense into it
you shape it and it comes back at you
filled with god energy
that's where you get someone starting a
cult i've heard from god everyone's
gotta
be castrated and the women need to do
this and we're all gonna kill ourselves
next thursday
that's someone who's connected to god
has no idea what they are
they haven't done their shadow work so
they yelled [ __ ] into god and heard it
you learned to empty yourself out to get
into the presence of god and actually
listen
and then instead of getting these weird
out of control delusions
yeah you get wisdom coming to you and i
think yeah
nonsense begins to become mythical and
instructive
yeah instead of destructive and even
like the way that you're talking about
your relationship with the world in
which
like you just kind of you articulated
right
i i think everything that you talked
about like i get this sense of like
you it's all been honing in on a
relationship
right it's like i would imagine there
was probably something about like
you know when the when the angel spoke
and instead
i projected my mother issue on it and
then i
thought it did like that wasn't quite it
but then you started to [ __ ] you started
to like hear it better
and then you could no i could just
imagine this a tuning
relationship and i think the thing you
just said i got this quality of like
oh yeah then there's that moment where
time goes away and i'm with
just with you and it's almost like all
of those structures
become one note right that like
that just goes in it's
in itself right this kind of sense where
i don't even have to
i don't have to think about any of this
stuff it it's implicit
something bleeds through yeah
that absolutely yeah
that and i think that there's a quality
in which when you talked about that
yeah it's like something just it just
drops in it just drops in
i don't even have to track it i just
it's just something that just drops in
i'm gonna see if i can bring some
language into this because this has just
started to kind of like come
into this thing i've been realizing
and this has been this is all part of
these conversations that i've been
having
with you with john and what's been great
is what's been great is about these
conversations that people can see
on the videos is you become friends i've
become friends with these people
and so there is this quality and i think
everybody can kind of can kind of get
this
like when you have a really deep
conversation ongoingly with somebody
they almost become a character that
speaks to you
like in when you're walking around when
they're not there they're like little
hints of reminding you of something
or something they said on some level you
start to realize that you are a constant
uh you're constantly in dialogue right
and you're in a
dielectric relationship right all the
way down on some level
but then you have i had these amazing
text exchanges
with with john and with chris
i i joked today i was i was i was like
man i have a feeling that you know
when we like way in the future when we
become like an ai thing like a billion
years from now it's going to
find us like an archaeology dick and
some old server and they're going to
pull the
our text exchange is up and they're
going to think it's like the dead sea
scrolls or something
because a lot of people with very
different frameworks whether it's like
ken wilber
but the integral stage or um dr greg
henriquez
where he's playing with that new plateau
um emerging
the way i frame that personally is that
i know
i experience that we're going through an
apocalypse
and an apocalypse is one of those words
that's bigger than i can explain
and yes it could mean we could be on the
verge
of destroying ourselves like if this
pandemic leads to something else
leads to america fighting with russia
fighting whoever we can actually blow
ourselves up which we've never been able
to before
but on the other hand what greg sees
emerging what ken wilber sees emerging
these are also apocalypses they're an
entire new level of reality
that has never existed before or that
it's an entire new world
if you view the world not as the dirt
and the
physical matter but the systems the
frameworks our mind world our
phenomenological
human world that it can't continue the
way it's been
we're either going to birth some sort of
golden age
or we're going to have some sort of
reset or self-destruction
and to me either is an apocalypse
and what an apocalypse is is also
something bigger than that
that i sense it i interact with that
energy
i know one name for it is apocalypse or
also to me it's obvious that we're in
revelation
because not only are all the dead sea
scrolls and the ancient
hermetic texts the emerald tablet like
things that people used to die and kill
to keep secrets
are now on the internet for everyone but
also our scientists
are now unveiling the word of god to us
by explaining like infinity theory by
cantor that lunatic mathematician
the way einstein and all of these people
are now saying look
like here's how reality works we that's
also to me
revelation of god's truth that has been
hidden from mankind up until now
and we're clearly at the point where to
plato and his buddies
we're in the apocalypse where we have
the power of gods
where i'm speaking at a chunk of plastic
that transforms it into a magical
language of ones and zeros
right then we transform that into zeus's
thunderbolts
send it halfway across the planet
and creates a magic portal of me yeah so
that we can communicate
right yes with electricity and hot
running water and the ability to
manipulate
genes and go to the moon and you know
yes we are god one day exists
but what are we gonna do with this
because we have the power of god without
the wisdom
and that's where we need people circling
or working on you know greg's program or
we need pajo and paul vander clay sam
harris to all get together and go whoa
we are
infant gods yeah we've got to grow up
here and
learn not to poop in our pants and blow
each other's hair
yeah totally
as you're talking about this i'm getting
i'm kind of get feeling the sense of
like
that which can tune into right
and and have something like the
apocalypse
make phenomenological sense right
like it's interesting there's
when you said i don't quite know exactly
what i mean exactly by that but i can
sense it right you can sense the energy
of it
it's thinking about this way that
the musicality of meaning that happens
in dialogue
right like there's a there's a quality
of like with
with music which is really interesting
to think about because i think
the way that you know you can be moved
by like a piece of i mean everybody's
been moved deeply by music
and it's it's it's a movement it's a
movement that you find
yourself already inside of right like
but there's no way you can put that into
words yet it's
that's the feeling of music and i think
it's very much
if you were to it's like if you were to
drop us right now right you could say
the like the the flow
of this dialogue which on some level is
is creating a world
that's like transparent and in some ways
it's like the world is like
uh withdrawing and becoming itself in
[Music]
us in characterizing each other right
this sense of moreness right we create a
third
thing like when we says when two or more
gather in my name
you and i form something a connection
flows
in the same way that between a positive
and negative node it can create an
arc of electricity it creates a third
thing that is its own thing
it appears to me as though we generate
things between us
when we in dragon we do it also in large
groups that's what rituals are for
and that's what concerts replicate for
the sake of entertainment
and also i was noticing very much how we
tend to frame it that everyone watching
this up until now
looks at it like i've been deciding what
i said
and that i'm the reason for the words
that come out of my mouth
but i show up to every one of these
things the same i clear out
i get into a moment of now i empty
myself
i get present and no expectation
so if you observe me talking to
different people
you'll realize guy's been in control
this entire time
everything i have said i would only have
said because he was here
i would have said it differently if
someone had asked me the same question
and so up till now it's looked like i
was in control of what i've said
you can watch this whole thing and if
you pay attention probably to my energy
you'll even pick up on it
i intuit that you're a good person god
i'm happy to let you
dr orrin amateur also i can sit down
with him it's fine you're in charge draw
whatever nonsense you want to
a dark manipulative person i would not
do that i would not go into a flow state
and let that dig
but with you my angel tells me it's safe
my third eye
says you're one of the midwives of the
apocalypse
and so i can simply let go yeah open
honest let anything that arises so in
that sense
you're in total control now of
everything i say until this podcast
ends also you're in total control of
when this podcast says
so i'm an instrument feel free to play
mercury however you wish
i really love what you just said like
you're you're a midwife of the
apocalypse
i i that's such a rich
that's a rich thing that you just said
like
midwifery you know
socrates
talked about listening is midwifery
right like and when i'm hurt
what i'm hearing you say it's like this
is very much
this is this mystery right this kind of
very almost spiritual
um embodied mystery that happens in
in connection with people is on some
level
it's like the ear calls out
calls out the one that speaks right
there's a way in which a
listening can be of such
deep musicality if you will that it
actually
has has the character go beyond
what their ability to sing is right
like there's a quality of of where i
think in a really really
rich conversation that what starts to
happen
is the thing that starts to realize that
it's real
it's it's the thing that's been doing
the talking is precisely the thing
that's listening
right and i so i really appreciate that
since i've always really
been fascinated with that quality
of yeah where there's a certain and this
is i think what you start to tune into
when you practice circling is
and to me circling is a magic ritual
yeah is what you're doing also a
conversation anything that's
right art is matched you know exactly
this is magic right this is divine and
we are
speaking ourselves into being as well as
reality around us
right so i look at all of this like
magical
business right not a ground level
business i work directly for upper
management
and i know that this is a magical thing
that i'm doing
to midwife the apocalypse and that i'm a
part of a bigger plan that i don't
know about and i don't need to know
about it's like
you know uh the way like confident or um
government works where it's a need to
know at my level i need i just get what
i need
to know to do my job i don't get any
other info
but to me this is all matter yeah well
that sense of
fact yeah responsibility that sense of
like that's i i just really like the
poetry of that sense of what you just
what you just said right
there of yeah there's a bigger plan
and i don't need to know what it is
right
and there's that quality of i think
that's a little bit what i was talking
about before
a little bit of about that
quality of
that that sense of moreness that doesn't
need to be
revealed it actually there's a way that
what i'm actually the what i have faith
in
right is that plan but the way that that
plan
i have faith isn't through knowing it
but actually
in a certain sense i hear it in the way
that i'm
i can let go right it's pres that
greater plan is present in the way that
i
find myself just fully here and letting
go
so it's present it's both is strangely
present and concealed at the same time
but that that that particular quality
just i thought that was really
beautifully said
and when people get mania that's when
you realize like mania can just set
everything on fire with me where every
number means everything
signs are sending you secret messages
butterflies are flying too
and again if you haven't done your
shadow work you'll warp that into
some sort of paranoid conspiracy or
you'll project your ideas
but as you progress you fine-tune it all
and you're like okay yeah everything
matters
it's all shining with glory like even
the dog [ __ ] on the street
and also each person means as much as
all of creation
so you can let go with someone and be
present with them and
and a part of you when you're not
comfortable yet with all this mushy [ __ ]
you and i are
connections a part of you is also right
that you're sacrificing the whole world
right now for me
all your loved ones that mean so much to
you you're not spending time with them
you've sacrificed the whole world to be
with me right now
and what you'll find though is each one
of us is worth that
and we'll experience that well everyone
experiences it with themselves
obviously you're worth the whole
universe to yourself
but you'll experience it with perhaps
your mother when you're young
perhaps your spouse or a child where
you're like oh my god
this baby means as much to me as all of
existence
when you go deep into the mysteries you
go oh [ __ ]
everyone means that much and the mother
father relationship you know to the
child is just revealing
something that's there with everyone
it's there in the homeless person you
walk by
it's not that they're not shining it's
you don't have the eyes to see
it you've still got the scales you
realize you can drop those and it's
wow [ __ ] each one of us is that precious
that
we're worth everything and then you
realize that
god's there is this great plan none of
us get left behind
this is and that one day everyone gets
to where i am where it's not just that
i'm okay with the difficulties i've been
through
i'm grateful for them i treasure them i
realize
my sorrow is what carves the canyon that
fills
my i realize the metaphysical reality
that
to build a layer of heaven into reality
you have to
dig a layer of health right that that
hell
serves us by creating heaven that
there's no inside
without an outside and that everything
including evil
including suffering it all serves the
good
and that in the end this is all divine
all
good no one gets left behind
there is no true injustice at the
highest level
it's a game we chose to play it's scary
it's x-rated
it's brutal it's full of you know sex
and rape and torture and just but also
bliss and ecstasy
but we're beings that want to do that
like alan watts says that we dare each
other like children
to jump into harder lives and to move
further from god
so that we can play peek-a-boo yeah
safety and divinity
oh my god i'm so lost peek-a-boo
okay so i get that that's the game we're
all playing and also that's why i don't
need
i don't need to save anyone anymore yeah
i don't need to go
teach anyone anything i'm happy to sit
back and i'll help whoever wants my
health
but if someone else wants like and if
collectively
if really what the majority of us need
to do and if our little project
fails and the other group and the world
i'm also fine with that if that's what's
best for everyone and
three years from now it's all mushrooms
clouds then
great i'll sit at humanity's bedside and
i'll you know sing you into the grave
like i'm happy to play that game
i don't care where the apocalypse goes
because i trust the greater plan
and either way it's worth living that
life to help us you're in a golden age
or to experience the end of something
is an amazing thing and so i'm up for
whatever game everyone wants to play
yeah yeah when you said when you said
like it's i'm think i'm not only
relieved that i i made it through some
of the
like the bad [ __ ] right but actually i'm
thankful for it
like i got this sense of and i would
imagine and it's interesting i think
this is the sense that i'm getting about
like
appreciating the ride that i'm getting
that you've been on
right and also hear what you're saying
on some level
it's actually in a very extreme way it's
it's the same architecture right it's
like
just the the veils are just um a lot
thinner right
with with the bipolar but i think what
i'm hearing you say is that
is that like in a manic state is it fair
to say
that like it's almost like everything
becomes an idol
right everything speaks it's almost kind
of like an idolatry
right where mania just connects you to
the higher realms
right and depression connects you to the
lower realms right
and for me my cycles lined up with the
year
so it's also mythical for me like the
ancient forest god
i'm born every spring i live mightily
through the summer
um i die in the fall and i spend my
winter in the crypt
um which you know is also i go into
heaven every summer and then i'm plunged
down into health
um you know like any good psychopal i go
through the cycle
and i've learned to go through it
non-judgmentally mindfully
and to be grateful for the whole process
yes because it's all serving the game
and just like
when i was a kid and star wars came out
and we were all
six on the playground we wanted to play
star wars every lunch hour
but no one wanted to be darth vader and
so i can remember if you got stuck being
darth vader you'd be like okay but
tomorrow i get to be luke
yeah so when i look at the villains in
the world now i don't hate them either
i didn't want to play the role of hitler
that's brutal
i think you know he deserves some love
and compassion
we should realize he hurts himself
everyone else yeah we're all responsible
for our own suffering it's for our own
good and i feel honored to get to play
on the good side right now
and i recognize i must have had to have
played the villain before
and you know i honor the people who are
you know if there is some new world
order conspiracy okay i get it because
we're playing star wars as grown-ups
and we need an empire to forge our jedi
and so they're doing a service by being
the emperor
or being vader and in that way lucifer
is does a service to all the universe
by testing us by going down into hell
to create the polarity so that we can
also experience heaven
and i see this as cooperative between
everything
just things need to learn their place
like demons have their place where they
serve
but you don't put them on the throne and
worship them yeah they're something to
be comforted
and present with and to learn certain
lessons from
yeah yeah it's funny as you talk about
is as you're talking about you're like
when i see just get a picture of your
life as you're talking
it's funny your life
shows up for me is almost like um
what do you call it uh uh icons
right where you know that whole thing
about an icon where it's like
you can see it's it's it that the
picture
isn't the thing it's what the it's what
the picture shines through
right and like oh my chest is trained
to be in a right relationship right on
my chest i have the black family motto
tattooed and it's
non-crooks said looks which means not
the cross but it's light
which meant not the church's idea of god
but whatever god is behind that and
that's what i've learned to believe in
is
i don't believe in my idea of god i
don't believe in the icon
i believe in whatever mystery is behind
that
totally and that i just really
appreciate i'm just
appreciating how with what you've
had to contend with the the icon at one
point
especially when you're manic it starts
to look like you're looking right at god
right
in this this real and what i'm hearing
is i'm sensing it's funny i'm sensing a
deep austerity in you
right in some sense of what i'm hearing
you say yeah i remain nothing
so that i can sufficiently not know the
greater plan in which i can trust
right and therefore there's something
about the world that shows up like that
that like
doesn't i don't get tricked
into that being i did not they're not
idols but that is what they shine
through and that relationship
i'm really sensing that kind of
how life or death that's been for you oh
yeah
absolutely like at some points 18 months
of solidly suicidal
like because it would be a two-year
depression center
the moment i wake up it's all [ __ ] i
woke up
and all day like to the point where at
times it's like i have to actively
stop myself from killing myself it's
like you know the way you'll suddenly
notice you're reaching for water and
your body's already doing it
where my body starts to get up to go
get like and i went through 18 months of
not a moment of relief
and it feels eternal it you believe it's
also when you're in hell
it completely alters all your memories
right when you can't remember being
happy easily yeah
and if someone reminds you or shows you
a picture of you happy
yeah you edit it you alter it and it
seems fake
i thought i was happy i wasn't i was
pretending and
when you look forward you're certain
you'll never
feel anything but this and in a way that
months is a turn you've never been happy
you can't remember
it seemed fake you never will be happy
it's suicidal all the way through
and if i wasn't
seriously concerned that i would exist
beyond
death i would have killed myself like if
i knew
or even thought it was most likely that
ricky gervais and richard dawkins were
right
then i would have been gone long ago
i suffered through what i considered to
be hell
i can't describe it any differently the
same way that christ
said in the gospel of thomas the kingdom
of god is laid before the eyes of men
yet they cannot see
amen to that also the deepest realm of
hell is laid before the eyes of men
and only those who are suicidal
you can tune right into a very low level
of health
that's what being suicidal is i consider
it dimension shift
it's not me reality itself also changes
it becomes hell to be on earth and if i
didn't believe
that i would go beyond the grave or at
least there were times where i wasn't
sure
but i couldn't take that risk that i was
going to end up somewhere
worse because a voice was telling you
can't kill yourself
you've got to suffer through this and
somehow that
voice that voice what i'm getting is
like
basically what you're saying it's like
time condenses
right like the hell that you're in it
takes over the entire future
and your entire past and this is now the
revelation of it's [ __ ] yeah and so
that's
everything everything blazes of that
black
fire or something right and yet there's
something you could hear
right and just barely early on totally
i'm impressed because i'm especially
impressed with this is what i think
like i think it's starting to more come
into an an image of what i sensed before
about oh yeah like the possibility and
the necessity
that you had to kind of they became the
same thing at one point because
i'm sitting in that i'm going like all
the horizons
are taken over and all there is is a
faint whisper
right and everything else is so
believable
and there's this little whisper and then
something that knows
to listen it's a faintest relationship
i'm like that's so unlikely
right that's so [ __ ] unlikely right
and i think it takes lots of us getting
plunged into it
for some of us to come out we're like
we're like a seed with a very low
germination rate and so even those
people who
don't pass that at that point they kill
themselves it's like
they're helping me it's we had to
scatter a hundred of us
to get one to grow some of you just take
one for the team
you're aware of the ones that took one
for the team right yeah there's
people who drown down there see this is
what's interesting this is what's
interesting is what i'm hearing is like
even in the compassion that this breeds
right because i hear it in your calling
them
here in the conversation right like you
made a point of just like
oh yeah and i realize that there's
probably other
like there's hundreds of us that have
kind of taken one for the team
and i get it and you caught like i
feel the sense of compassion or like
soldiers
crossing to the next trench and almost
everyone gets mowed down but that's why
i made it across
is because 10 000 of us ran for the line
and just one or two of us make it there
so everyone who fell behind us
it's our job to go back for them or
just set up the world for them so when
they're reborn
they get a better chance a real kind of
cosmic sense
a cosmic sense of indebtedness yes right
and that's why like one of my magical
jobs
is being a cycle pump and one thing i do
with the channel
is i work with some suicidal people
where they're in health
i can't change that immediately but what
i can do is i can go right down into
health i know how to go in there
and i'm friends with the demons i'm
allowed to pass i'm murderers
i'm allowed to go into hell and i'm
allowed to go back out i'm a psychopath
and i can meet people down there yeah
and i can say it's okay
i'll be pres the same way with azrael
the way he's like i
can't hurt my angel um i can't take you
out right now
yeah but trust me you can get out i can
go down with them
into hell and like many empaths train to
learn to block
like to shield so that they can survive
the world instead i've learned to
channel
like to let flow like when i got hit by
light just let it flow through
and be non-judgmental present with it
so i can drop into hell and i can
connect to someone where i'm crying too
and i'm feeling it
yes we're in health
experience i i'm gonna be fine
i'm gonna go back out here and i can't
take you with me directly
yeah i can keep coming and meeting you
here right and coming back out just so
you know
it's a way out and so that if you're not
hearing the voice that's sticking
through
like don't take the risk that it's worse
i'm noticing i'm getting a sense of just
first of all
like i'm kind of finding myself being
that person in hell and imagine it like
i was just picturing you coming in and
going back out and coming in
it's almost like i get i it's
interesting
i can hear from being that person i can
begin to hear you as like an
agent of that voice that little whisper
right i get the sense like i can imagine
you saying look
i can't even have you make you hear the
whisper
all i can be is an evident that there's
a whisper that you can start to hear and
you're hearing me
and something maybe at some point that
that that starts to awaken
they start to hear the whisper within
all of that
right because sometimes we can see
things more easily and others than
ourselves so
yeah and it's really hard especially
when you're insane to value yourself
like
until until i learned to accept that i
was now insane
just tried to learn how to be insane the
first five years i was trying to get
back to normal
to hammer myself back into something
and instead i had to accept it but to
learn to love yourself when you're in
hell
and when you're legally insane and
useless to society is hard
but other people can see it me they
can't love themselves yet
but they can love me and so if i can go
down there and be like hey no no i'm you
i've been here i see i can show you by
coming back
and if you see it in me you're worth as
much
as i'm yeah yeah let's get you out of
here too
because we're all one being and none of
us will be finally satisfied
until all of us have gotten through our
trials and tribulations
right and then after seeing and for me
it required there's this musician
sasha degrow who's uh the bass player
for the band choking victim
er like used to be and i my sister
burned me a copy of them
doing a live performance on the radio
and at this point i was in a depression
i didn't want to live i didn't want to
be insane i couldn't accept
i didn't know what to do with it and i'm
listening to this cd and at one point in
between
songs like the disc jockey the radio guy
asks sasha about his organization with
uh insane people and sasha just casually
mentions that he's bipolar
and turns out he's the same kind of
bipolar as me
type one with psychotic features he
experienced end of world delusions you
know
hospitalization and here he was casually
discussing
everyone's treating him with respect and
he's just doing like a reunion playing
with the band he's moved on where he's
made his life
about you know discovering what it is to
be insane
and to treat it like a dangerous gift
rather than a mental illness
yeah and at first i was able to accept
that he was bipolar
before i could accept that i was and i
recently did a podcast with him
to introduce him to the audience
so now i'm serving the role to other
people
that he once served for me hey you're an
insane mess that barely understands
reality cool
right that's me too like we're the same
tribe right and i'm fine with it and
check it out like real people take me
seriously
look how nice guys being to this
ridiculous lunatic
you have value too it doesn't matter how
insane you are
right aim at the good do your best
that's all we need you to do
yeah absolutely absolutely
yeah i can just feel that solidarity and
that sense of humility
and the sense of indebtedness and it's
interesting because i'm just like as
we're talking i'm just kind of getting a
it's like something like um
just you know in some way and first of
all i really i appreciate what you're
talking about like being in hell i
definitely
i mean like i mean i've
gone through a lot of trauma and i've
had some i've gone through some pretty
intense [ __ ] emotional states that
have just swallowed me up and i've been
you know as hospitalized when i was a
teenager
for like having all kinds of breakdowns
and
so i've definitely been to like at some
emotional
deep emotional landscapes um
and i think i there's something about
this conversation where i'm starting to
start to really
get more of a sense through what you're
talking about
in a more articulated way of
that being us is in such relationship
right to so many different things right
like
and it's it's being us is as much
granted by the world like the deeper
world that we're in that
that comes through us and it's that
sense of
knowing the right thing to listen to
right and that tuning in
that you can't really take credit for
but you submit like there's a there's a
sense of like
where everything elicits so many
responses and you gotta like
you have to you have to battle with
yourself and you're like no
that thing right there is a different
color than everything else
and i just something tells me just keep
keep at that
that that that's actually our self
is developed through that time and
there's something about the way that
you're talking about it and how
literal it's been for you that's really
having me see
more of the structures of the things
that
i'm looking at and working with it's
really great
that's beautiful i and again with this i
had no idea where this conversation was
gonna go i was just
jumping in in faith that we find
something good but yeah
yeah if i can be of assistance to you
and your project
i completely see you're shining with the
light of
this bigger project and i'm at your
disposal like
upper management's making it clear to me
that if you need anything like as long
as i've got the ability
to do it yes i will yes
so nice to meet you my friend yes
absolutely
yeah speaking of calling i'm hearing my
wife in the background
all right well i think that's a great
place to wrap up
[Music]
you